<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UVCE Connect</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Open</string>
    <string name="title_activity_test">test</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_drawer">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_uvce">about_uvce</string>
    <string name="large_text">
       "University Visvesvaraya College of Engineering (UVCE) was established in 1917, under the name Government Engineering College, by Bharat Ratna Sir M. Visvesvaraya, and was then affiliated to Bangalore University."
        "It is the fifth engineering college to be established in the country."
        "UVCE is a constituent college of Bangalore University which gives it a special status of a university."
        "UVCE is one of the few technical institutions in the country that is vested with the status of a university."
        "It is one of the oldest technical institutions in the country, imparting technical education leading to B.E, B.Arch, M.E, M.Arch and PhD degrees in the various disciplines of Engineering and Architecture."
        "The college is approved by the AICTE and the Government of Karnataka."
        "The departments are accredited with five A+ for three years by the National Board of Accreditation, New Delhi. UVCE has a NAAC rating of five stars for the past four consecutive years."
        "The college receives financial aid under the TEQIP program from the World Bank."
    </string>

    <string name="quickstart_message">Click the SUBSCRIBE TO NEWS button below to subscribe to the
        news topic. Messages sent to the news topic will be received. The LOG TOKEN button logs the
        InstanceID token to logcat.</string>
    <string name="subscribe_to_news">Subscribe To News</string>
    <string name="log_token">Log Token</string>

    <string name="msg_subscribed">Subscribed to news topic</string>
    <string name="msg_token_fmt" translatable="false">InstanceID Token: %s</string>

    <string name="default_notification_channel_id" translatable="false">fcm_default_channel</string>
    <!--
            This is the name that users will see when interacting with this channel.
            It should describe the category of notifications that will be sent through this channel
         -->
    <string name="default_notification_channel_name" translatable="true">News</string>
    <string name="msg_subscribe_failed">Failed to subscribe to news topic</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>

